EnglishРусский한국어

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The safety of your personal data is important to us, here at Alicia Online we are committed to protecting your personal data and keeping you informed on how this data is used.

Please be sure to read this Privacy Policy before using this site or submitting information to us. This policy may change from time to time, so please check this page periodically for updates. If we make any major changes to our policies, we will put a notice on our website.

**1\. Data that Alicia Online collects from you**

The Alicia Online website uses "Cookies" to make it easier for you to access and use your account, and ensure the web pages are displayed correctly in your browser. The collected data is kept completely private and is not shared with anyone.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small pieces of information that are remembered in your browser. Alicia Online uses cookies to allow faster access when you revisit the website and to ensure proper display of the web pages.

**What data is collected and why?**

\- Email address  
This is the email you provide to register your account, it can be used to recover access to your account if you ever have login problems.

\- Login data  
This data is what you use to login, it's also how the website remembers if you are already logged in.

\- Browser details  
This is used to adjust the website's web pages to display correctly on your browser. This includes your preferred language settings and size adjustments for images and text.

**2\. How Alicia Online protects your data**

We work hard to protect your personal data. We use both technical and procedural methods to maintain the integrity and security of our databases, SSL encryption for data transfer, firewalls, and restricted access to data.

The safety and security of your data also depends on you. You should never share your account information such as your password or login with anyone else. If you believe anyone has unauthorized access to your account you should contact us promptly.

**3\. Choices you have about how Alicia Online uses your data**

You may send us a message on our Facebook page to request, review, correct or delete any personal data maintained on our systems that you provided to us through account registration.

If you do not wish us to collect cookies, you may set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that this might limit functionality of some elements on the website.

**4\. How to contact Alicia Online**

You can send us a message at our [VK page](https://vk.com/alicia_english).

Last Revision: June 14th 2018
